Finding Aid for the Lejaren Hiller Collection of Audio Tape Recordings, 1958-1985
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD, for 1 to 7 harpsichords and 1 to 51 tapes (1968), composed with John Cage (H. 41), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, Tail out,; Master Copy B 29-30-31 (Reel IX of 18) Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 102)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD, for 1 to 7 harpsichords and 1 to 51 tapes (1968), composed with John Cage (H. 41), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, Tail out,; Master Copy B 32-33-34 (Reel X of 18) Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 103)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD, for 1 to 7 harpsichords and 1 to 51 tapes (1968), composed with John Cage (H. 41), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, Tail out,; Master Copy B 35-36-37 (Reel XI of 18) Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 104)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD, for 1 to 7 harpsichords and 1 to 51 tapes (1968), composed with John Cage (H. 41), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, Tail out,; Master Copy B 38-39-40 (Reel XII of 18) Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 105)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD, for 1 to 7 harpsichords and 1 to 51 tapes (1968), composed with John Cage (H. 41), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, Tail out,; Master Copy B 41-42-43 (Reel XIII of 18) Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 106)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD, for 1 to 7 harpsichords and 1 to 51 tapes (1968), composed with John Cage (H. 41), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, Tail out,; Master Copy B 44-45-46 (Reel XIV of 18) Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 107)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD, for 1 to 7 harpsichords and 1 to 51 tapes (1968), composed with John Cage (H. 41), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, Tail out,; Master Copy B 47-48-49 (Reel XV of 18) Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 108)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD, for 1 to 7 harpsichords and 1 to 51 tapes (1968), composed with John Cage (H. 41), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, Tail out,; Master Copy B 50-51-52 (Reel XVI of 18) Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 109)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD, for 1 to 7 harpsichords and 1 to 51 tapes (1968), composed with John Cage (H. 41), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, Tail out,; Master Copy B 53-54-55 (Reel XVII of 18) Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 110)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD, for 1 to 7 harpsichords and 1 to 51 tapes (1968), composed with John Cage (H. 41), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, Tail out,; Master Copy B Gam. 56 only (Reel XVIII of 18) Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 111)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD - Buffalo Production (H. 41), Performance of March 23, 1980, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Performance Reel 1 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 112)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD - Buffalo Production (H. 41), Performance of March 23, 1980, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Performance Reel 2 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 113)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD - Buffalo Production (H. 41), Performance of March 23, 1980, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Performance Reel 3 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 114)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD - Buffalo Production (H. 41), Performance of March 23, 1980, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Performance Reel 4 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 115)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD - Buffalo Production (H. 41), Performance of March 23, 1980, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Performance Reel 5 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 116)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD - Solos 1, 2 and 3 (H. 41), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Sub-masters of solos Submaster Performers: Solo I is played by David Tudor on a Baldwin Electronic Harpsichord; Solo II is played by Antoinette Vischer on a Neupert Bach-model Harpsichord Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 117)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD - Solo VI (H. 41), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo; Submaster tapes Submaster Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 118)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD - Tape Collage (H. 41), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Master tape Duration: 21:00 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 119)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD - Tape Collage #2 (H. 41), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Duration: 21:00 Approximately 2/3 of the performance tapes. Channel 1 - tracks 1, 3, 4, 6, 7 of 8-channel Master A Channel 2 - tracks 1, 2, 4, 5, 7, 8 of 8-channel Master B Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 120)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD - Tape Collage #3 (H. 41), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Duration: 21:00 Approximately 1/3 of the performance tapes. Channel 1 - tracks 1, 4, 7 of 8-channel Master A Channel 2 - tracks 2, 5, 8 of 8-channel Master B Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 121)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD - for Nonesuch Recording (H. 41), Recorded January 23, 1969, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, Tail out,; Master tapes Copy no. 2 Duration: 21:00 Master Tape #1 Channel 1 - channels 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8 of 8-channel Master A Channel 3 - channels 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8 of 8-channel Master B Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 122)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD - for Nonesuch Recording (H. 41), Recorded January 23, 1969, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, Tail out,; Master tapes Copy no. 2 Duration: 21:00 Master Tape #2 Channel 1 - channels 1, 3, 4, 6, 7 of 8-channel Master A Channel 3 - channels 1, 2, 4, 5, 7, 8 of 8-channel Master B Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 123)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD - for Nonesuch Recording (H. 41), Recorded January 23, 1969, 1 10 inch reel; speed unknown, Tail out,; Master tapes Copy no. 2 Duration: 21:00 Master Tape #3 Channel 1 - channels 1, 4, 7 of 8-channel Master A Channel 3 - channels 2, 5, 8 of 8-channel Master B Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 124)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 HPSCHD - Collage for Nonesuch Record (H. 41), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel stereo.; Sub-master Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 125)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Algorithms I, for nine instruments and tape (Versions I-IV) (1968) (H. 42), undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo.; Cue tapes Duplicate of Master tape 130 versions 1-4 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 126)
  Version 1 Cue 1- 1st movement; Cue 2- 2nd movement; Cue 3- 3rd movement, 1st entry Cue 4- 3rd movement, 2nd entry Version 2 Cue 1; Cue 2; Cue 3; Cue 4 Version 3 Cue 1; Cue 2; Cue 3; Cue 4 Version 4 Cue 1; Cue 2; Cue 3; Cue 4
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Algorithms I, for nine instruments and tape (Versions I-IV) (1968) (H. 42), undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips; Cue tape Duplicate of Master tape 130 versions 1-4; each version separated by 12 seconds of leader tape Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 127)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Algorithms I, for nine instruments and tape (Versions I-IV) (1968) (H. 42), undated, 1 7 inch reel; speed unknown; Duplicate of Master Tape 129 Performers: Members of the Center for the Creative and Performing Arts; Lejaren Hiller, conductor (version I and IV); Jan Williams, conductor (version II); Bruce Hengen (?) conductor, Rochester 3/17/73 (version III). Duration: 9:15; 9:15; 9:25; 9:15 Tape digitally reformatted: No (Item 128)
  a.) The Decay of Information b.) Icosahedron c.) The Incorporation of Constraints
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Algorithms I, for nine instruments and tape (Versions I-IV) (1968) (H. 42), undated, 1 10 inch reel; speed unknown; Master tape Master performance tape Performers: Lejaren Hiller, conductor, Version I and IV; Version II: Concert Performance, Jan Williams Version III: Concert Performance, Eastman “Musica Nova” conducted by Bruce Hengen Duration: 9:15 (version 1); 9:16 (version 2) Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 129)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Algorithms I, for nine instruments and tape (1968) (H. 42), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Cue tape master Master cue tapes Three movements, four versions each. Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 130)
  First Movement: The Decay of Information Version 1-4 Second Movement: Icosahedron Version 1-4 Third Movement: The Incorporation of Constraints Version 1-4
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Algorithms I, for nine instruments and tape (Versions I-IV) (1968) (H. 42), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips; Cue tape Probably duplicate of Tape 130; include as backup? Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 131)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Computer music, for percussion and tape (1968), composed with G. Allan O'Conner (H. 43a), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 7 ½ and 15 ips, 2-channel stereo., B. Dolby A - noise reduction; Master tape Master tape, including cues Performers: A. Performed by G. Allan O'Connor; 6:45 B. Performed by Jan Williams; 6:40 (Dolby A - noise reduction encoded master) C. 15 ips Cue tape - corrected D. 7 ½ Cue tape - corrected [E.] Storage copy of quartet version of "Computer Music" - 7 ½ ips; performed by Laurence Trott, Martha Herr, John Boudler, and tape Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 132)
  I. Assertively 3:33 II. Briskly 0:58 III. Lyrically 2:01
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Computer music, for soprano, piccolo, percussion and tape (1981) (H. 43), undated, 1 7 inch reel; speed unknown; Cue tapes Possible different versions of cues Notes on container: 2 copies (2nd not corrected; 1st: master copy; corrected 2nd movement; complete again with 15 and 7 ½ ips) Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 133)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Three rituals, for two percussion, projections and lights (1969) (H. 44), Recorded May 1, 1971, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo.; Performance Performers: Dennis Kahle and Jeffrey Kowalsky, percussion Duration: 30:48 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 134)
  I. The First Ritual 9:12 II. The Second Ritual 7:06 III. The Third Ritual 14:22
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Three rituals, for two percussion, projections and lights (1969) (H. 44), undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo.; Cue tape (for last movement) Cue tape Channel A: Percussion recording Channel B: Click track (Spine label also says "Quartet No. 5 - Rhythm tape) Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 135)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Sonata, No. 3 for violin and piano (1970) (H. 45), H. 45 recorded May 10, 1971, 1 7 inch reel; speed unknown; Performance of H. 50 is duplicated Tape 155, which is quadraphonic; include for stereo. format Performers: H. 45: Sokol, violin; Roger Shields, piano H. 50: Keiko Furness, Linda Mabrey Duration: 15:30 (H. 45); Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 136)
  I. Furioso 3:32 II. Largo 7:54 III. Prestissimo 3:56
  H. 50, Six easy pieces, for violin and piano (1974) I. Cowboy Song II. Rainy Day III. Soda Pop IV. Wadzel’s Catnap V. The Tin Man VI. Time To Go
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Cenotaph, for two pianos (1971) (H. 46), Recorded March 1983, 1 7 inch reel; speed unknown; Duplicate of Tape 29 Performers: Frina and Kenwyn Boldt, pianos Duration: 17:37 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 137)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Sonata, No. 6 for piano "Rage over the lost Beethoven" (1972) Part 1 (H. 47a), undated, 1 7 inch reel; speed unknown; Duplicate of Master Tape 140 Performers: Stephen Manes, piano Duration: 24:10 Tape digitally reformatted: No (Item 138)
  I. Rage Over the Lost Composer
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Sonata, No. 6 for piano "Rage over the lost Beethoven" (1972) Part 2 (H. 47a), undated, 1 7 inch reel; speed unknown; Duplicate of Master tape 141 Performers: Michael Collier, Roger Shields, piano Duration: 26:24 Tape digitally reformatted: No (Item 139)
  II. Rage Over the Lost Artifacts 6:46 III. Rage Over the Lost Spirit 19:32
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Sonata, No. 6 for piano "Rage over the lost Beethoven" (1972) Part 1 (H. 47a), Recorded March 4, 1972, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel stereo.; Master tape Performers: Stephen Manes, piano Duration: 24:10 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 140)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Sonata, No. 6 for piano "Rage over the lost Beethoven" (1972) Part 2 (H. 47a), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel stereo.; Master tape Performers: II: Michael Collier, piano; recorded March 20, 1972 III: Roger Shields, piano; recorded May 9, 1972 Duration: 26:22 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 141)
  II. Rage Over the Lost Artifacts 6:46 0:04 III. Rage Over the Lost Spirit 19:32
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Sonata, No. 6 for piano "Rage over the lost Beethoven" (1972) (H. 47a), undated, 1 10 inch reel; speed unknown; Unique performance Performers: Alan Mandel, piano Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 142)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Rage over the lost Beethoven (1972), composed with Frank Parman (H. 47b), undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Voice tapes - dub Duplicate of Tape 146 (a) tape one for machine #1 (b) tape two for machine #2 Tape digitally reformatted: No (Item 143)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Rage over the lost Beethoven (1972), composed with Frank Parman. Part 1 (H. 47b), First performance of February 20, 1972 at the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, Buffalo, N.Y., 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo.; Duplicate of Master tape 147 Duration: 23:24 Tape digitally reformatted: No (Item 144)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Rage over the lost Beethoven (1972), composed with Frank Parman. Part 2 (H. 47b), First performance of February 20, 1972 at the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, Buffalo, N.Y., 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo.; Duplicate of Master tape 148 Duration: 29:41 Tape digitally reformatted: No (Item 145)
  II. Rage Over the Lost Artifacts 7:22 III. Rage Over the Lost Spirit 22:19
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Rage over the lost Beethoven (1972), composed with Frank Parman (H. 47b), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Voice tapes Alternate source - Tape 143 (a) Tape No. 1 for Machine #1 (b) Tape No. 2 for Machine #2 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 146)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Rage over the lost Beethoven (1972), composed with Frank Parman (H. 47b), First performance of February 20, 1972 at the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, Buffalo, N.Y., 1 10 inch reel; 15 and 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo, Tail out; Master tape Master tape Alternate source - Tape 144 Part I: Rage over the lost Composer, Rage over the lost Artifacts; 23:28 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 147)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Rage over the lost Beethoven (1972), composed with Frank Parman (H. 47b), First performance of February 20, 1972 at the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, Buffalo, N.Y., 1 10 inch reel; 15 and 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo, Tail out; Master tape Master tape Alternate source - Tape 144 Part II: Rage over the lost Spirit Voice tape master - for cue tapes for performances of Beethoven's, F. Hiller's, Hummel's voices, etc."; 7 ½ ips Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 148)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Rage over the lost Beethoven (1972), composed with Frank Parman (H. 47b), First performance of February 20, 1972 at the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, Buffalo, N.Y., 1 10 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Sub-master Submaster Duplicate of Tapes 148-149; include due to concerns about how the tapes are labeled Performers: Terry Moore, theatrical director; Stephen Manes, Michael Collier, and Roger Shields Duration: ca. 53:05 Music is Sonata No. 6 for Piano (1972) Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 149)
  I. Rage Over The Lost Composer 23:24 II. Rage Over The Lost Artifacts 7:22 III. Rage Over The Lost Spirit 22:19
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Algorithms II, for nine instruments and tape (1972), composed with Ravi Kumra (H. 48), undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, Tail out,; Cue tapes Duplicate of Master tape 153 Versions 1-4 (Cue tapes run the full length of the composition) Tape digitally reformatted: No (Item 150)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Algorithms II, for nine instruments and tape (1972), composed with Ravi Kumra (H. 48), Recorded September 1985 in Warsaw, Poland, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo.; Duplicate of Master tape 152 Performers: Warsaw Ensemble; Jan Williams, conductor Versions 1-4 Tape digitally reformatted: No (Item 151)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Algorithms II, for nine instruments and tape (1972), composed with Ravi Kumra (H. 48), undated, 1 10 inch reel; speed unknown, Dolby A,; Master tape Master performance tape Master tape of Warsaw performance Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 152)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Algorithms II, for nine instruments and tape (1972), composed with Ravi Kumra (H. 48), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Cue tape masters; Performance masters Master cue and performance tapes Version 1-4 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 153)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 String quartet No. 6 (1972) (H. 49), Recorded June 19, 1973, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo.; Duplicate performance of Tape 155, but in stereo. format Performers: Concord String Quartet Duration: 23:41 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 154)
  I. Arrabiato 6:00 II. Tranquillo 8:23 III. Vivace 9:10 0:08
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 String quartet No. 6 (1972) (H. 49), H. 49 recorded June 19, 1973; H. 50 (1.) recorded June 21, 1975, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 4 channel quadraphonic., Tail out; Master tape Master, but quadraphonic format Performers: H. 49: Concord String Quartet H. 50: 1.Benjamin Hudson, violin; Joseph Kubera, piano; 2. Keiko Furness, violin; Linda Mabrey, piano Duration: 23:41 (H. 49); 6:41 (H. 50) Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 155)
  I. Arrabiato 6:00 II. Tranquillo 8:23 III. Vivace 9:10
  H. 50, Six easy pieces, for violin and piano (1974) I. Cowboy Song 0:57 II. Rainy Day 2:21 III. Soda Pop 0:30 IV. Wadzel’s Catnap 0:57 V. The Tin Man 0:35 VI. Time to Go 1:01
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Cue tapes 1-4 Duplicate of Tape 165 Performance Tape No. 1 - "Timing Tape"; 21:30 Tape digitally reformatted: No (Item 156)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Cue tapes 1-4 Duplicate of Tape 166 Performance Tape No. 2 - "Harmony Tape"; 20:08 Tape digitally reformatted: No (Item 157)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Cue tapes 1-4 Duplicate of Tape 167 Performance Tape No. 3 - "Bell Tape"; 19:04 Tape digitally reformatted: No (Item 158)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Cue tapes 1-4 Duplicate of Tape 168 Performance Tape No. 4 - "Canon Tape"; 18:00 Tape digitally reformatted: No (Item 159)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 4 channel quadraphonic, DBX, tail out; Cue tape Quadraphonic format cue tape Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 160)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo., tail out; Cue tape "for trip" Cue tape "for trip" - unclear contents Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 161)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), undated, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo., head out; Tape collage Tape collage - unclear contents Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 162)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), Recorded October 1978, 1 7 inch reel; 7 ½ ips, 2-channel stereo.; Duplicate of Tape 179 Performers: Frances-Marie Uitti, cello Cello version Tape digitally reformatted: No (Item 163)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), Instrumental version recorded June 9, 1976; Vocal version recorded May 1978, 1 7 inch reel; speed unknown; Duplicate of Tape 178 Performers: Instrumental version: members of the Center of the Creative and Performing Arts conducted by Jan Williams; Vocal version: Gregg Smith Singers conducted by Gregg Smith Vocal and instrumental versions Tape digitally reformatted: No (Item 164)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel stereo, Tail out; 15 Cue tapes Cue tapes Performance Tape No. 1 - "Timing Tape"; 21:30 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 165)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel stereo, Tail out; 15 Cue tapes Cue tapes Performance Tape No. 2 - "Harmony Tape"; 20:08 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 166)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel stereo, Tail out; 15 Cue tapes Cue tapes Performance Tape No. 3 - "Bell Tape"; 19:04 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 167)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel stereo, Tail out; 15 Cue tapes Cue tapes Performance Tape No. 4 - "Canon Tape"; 18:00 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 168)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel; Cue tape Cue tapes Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 169)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips (38 cm/sec.), 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Cue tapes No. 1-4 / Master tape Master cue tapes Cue tape No. 1; Performance Tape No. 1 - "Timing Tape", 21:30 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 170)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips (38 cm/sec.), 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Cue tapes No. 1-4 / Master tape Master cue tapes Cue tape No. 2; Performance Tape No. 2 - "Harmony Tape", 20:08 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 171)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips (38 cm/sec.), 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Cue tapes No. 1-4 / Master tape Master cue tapes Cue tape No. 3; Performance Tape No. 3 - "Bell Tape", 19:04 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 172)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips (38 cm/sec.), 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Cue tapes No. 1-4 / Master tape Master cue tapes Cue tape No. 4; Performance Tape No. 4 - "Canon Tape", 18:00 Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 173)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 4 channel, Tail out,; Master tape Four-channel master tape "Four-Channel Master Tape" Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 174)
- Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Portfolio, for diverse performers and tapes (1974) (H. 51), undated, 1 10 inch reel; 15 ips, 2-channel stereo., Tail out; Master tape Master 2-channel tape Duration: 21:28 "(2-channel tape only version)' Tape digitally reformatted: Yes (Item 175)